McKersie, Robert B. Arbitration, Civil Rights, and Interrogation Files 6958
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Notes from a Movie: "Sophie Schul", 2007 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Intelligence Science Board February Meeting, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Matching Interests to Strategy, Strategy to Tactics, Tactics to Leverage?, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Components of our Case Study Development Project and an Illustrative Analysis of Jandal Case Study, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Pre-Soaking Process, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Tasks at Hand and Future Research Options, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Toward a "Model B" in Educing Information Operations, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Intelligence Science Board Mach Meeting, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- EIP Questions, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- The Myths Have Morphed into Questions, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Jeffrey H. Smith: A War Under Law, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Study on Educating Information, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Infidel by Ayaan Hirsi Ali, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Sources of Power and Leverage in El for the EIT and EIP, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Thinking of the Activity of Interrogating High-Value Detainees as a Profession, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Part II, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Human Rights First, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Manuscript Framework, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Items for our Discussions (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Jess Bravin: The Conscience of the Colonel, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Interrogation of a Panamanian Air Force Colonel during the Invasion of Panama, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Battle of Wits v Battle of Wills, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Correspondence Regarding Case Studies for the Phase 2 Reports, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Arthur Bright: Report: Israel's Shin Bet Uses Torture Illegally in Interrogations, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Framework Paper, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Charles C. Krulak and Joseph P. Hoar: "It's Our Cage, Too", 2007 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Interrogation of a Republican Guard During the Gulf War, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Framework Proposals, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- The Interrogation of Nguyen Tai: master Spy for the North Vietnamese, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- John Ydstie: U.S. Panel Shapes New Interrogation Guidelines, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Educator Strategies and Tactics: A Negotiation Framework, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Input for the Research Agenda, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Research, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Intelligence Science Board Meeting, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Whether to Include the BATNA, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Choice Points and the Call for Guidelines, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Analyzing An Interrogation Transcript, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Peter Suedfeld: Torture, Interrogation, Security, and Psychology: Absolutistic versus Complex Thinking, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- The CIA's Torture Teachers, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Thoughts the Morning After, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Bryan's Feedback on the Manuscript, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Custodial Educing Information Experiences, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Questions about Operational Accord, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- The Interrogation of Bin Laden's Bodyguard, Abu Jandal, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Katherine Eban: The War on Terror, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Basic Ideas, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Jackson Diehl: Pistachios at Guantanamo, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Vicky Nanjappa: Exclusive: Haneef Mohammed's Interrogation in Australia, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Fran Townsend: White House HLS Advisor on Detainee Interrogation Program, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Bernard Carey, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Report: Harsh Methods Used On 9/11 Suspect, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Jane Mayer: The Black Sites, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Excerpts from Hayden Interview with Charlie Rose, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Benedict Carey: You Remind Me of Me, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Call for Presidential Ban on Torture, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Perspectives on the Functioning of a Counter-Terrorism Intelligence System, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Ordeal in Iran: An Interview with Haleh Esfandiari, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Interrogation Survey: Beacon Hill Seminar, Fall 2008 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Blind Spots II: The Interrogation Game. Couse Syllabus, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Close Out of Consultant Agreement with MITRE, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Steven Kleiman: Try a Little Tenderness, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- David Rock: Managing with the Brain in Mind, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Information about the December 10-11 Meeting, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Day After Thought, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Supporting the HIG: Finding a Way Forward in Interrogation Research, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Richard E. Walton: Advantages and Attributes of the Case Study, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Arab Cultural Awareness: 58 Factsheets. Tradoc DCSINT Handbook No.2, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Steven M. Kleinman: Barriers to Success: Critical Challenges in Developing a New Educing Information Paradigm, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Michael E. Gaffney: Better Bargaining. Annotated Draft (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Michael E. Gaffney: Better Bargaining, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Dominic Streatfield: Brainwash: The Secret History of Mind Control, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Kenneth J. Levit: The CIA and the Torture Controversy: Interrogation Authorities and Practices in the War on Terror, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Cage prisoners, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Edgar H. Schein: Coercive Persuasion: A Socio-psychological Analysis of the "Brainwashing" of American Civilian Prisoners by the Chinese Communists, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Communications Workers of America: Committee on the Future Report, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Consensus Decision-Making. Leader's Guide (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Alfred W. McCoy: Cruel Science: CIA Torture and U.S. Foreign Policy, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 79)
- Charles A Morgan III: Detecting Deception in Arabic: Efficacy of Force-Choice Testing Dilemmas in Moroccans (Box 6, Folder 80)
- Educing Information: Developing the U.S. Capacity (Box 6, Folder 81)
- Daniel L. Shapiro: Enemies, Allies, and Emotions, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 82)
- G. Daniel Lassiter: Evaluating Videotaped Confessions, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 83)
- Experiences to Go: Teaching with Intelligence Case Studies. Joint Military Intelligence College, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 84)
- R.F. and H.J. Scharff: Fighters Behind Fences, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 85)
- Harrah's Showboat Negotiations, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 86)
- Mark Bowden: How to Break A Terrorist, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 87)
- Daniel L. Shapiro: Identity is More Than Meets the "I": The Power of Identity in Shaping Negotiation Behavior, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 88)
- Paul Lehner: Intelligence Analysis: Predict, Forecase, Anticipate, and Project, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 89)
- Interest-Based Problem Solving, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 90)
- Herbert C. Kelman: Interests, Relationships, Identities: Three Central Issues for Individuals and Groups in Negotiation Their Social Environment, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 91)
- Richard E. Walton: Interpersonal Confrontation and Basic Third Party Functions: A Case Study, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 92)
- Edward G. Stockdale: Interrogation of Kamikaze Pilot (Box 6, Folder 93)
- Greg Miller and Chris Macken: The Interrogators Inside the Secret War Against Al Qaeda, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 94)
- Issue Resolution Facilitator's Guide (Box 6, Folder 95)
- JTF-GTMO Information on Detainees, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 96)
- Cheryl Stewart: Joint Interrogation Facility, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 97)
- Thomas A. Kochan: The Kaiser Permanente Labor Management Partnership 2009-2013 (Box 6, Folder 98)
- Steven M. Kleinman: MIS-Y: A Case Study in Strategic Interrogation, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 99)
- Making Consultation Work: The Important of Process, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 100)
- Garth Mangum: Memorandum of Negotiations and Negotiating Methods (Box 6, Folder 101)
- The Must-Do List, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 102)
- Samuel Hughes: National Insecurity, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 103)
- The Negotiating Patterns of Practicing Lawyers, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 104)
- Daniel L. Shapiro: Negotiating Emotions, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 105)
- Daniel L. Shapiro: A Negotiator's Guide to Emotion: Four 'Laws' to Effective Practice, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 106)
- Richards J. Heuer, Jr.: Nosenko: Five Paths to Judgement, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 107)
- On Torture, 2 Messages and a High Political Cost. Scott Shane, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 108)
- Adam Zagorin: One Life Inside Gitmo, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 109)
- Paul Lehner: Options for Scientific Research on Education Practices, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 110)
- POW Holding Facility (Box 6, Folder 111)
- Ilai Alon and Jeanne Brett: Perceptions of Time and Their Impact on Negotiations in the Arabic-Speaking Islamic World, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 112)
- Sanford Levinson: "Precommitment" and "Postcommitment" The Ban On Torture In The Wake of September 11, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 113)
- Daniel L. Shapiro: Preempting Disaster: Pre-Mediation Strategies to Deal with Strong Emotions, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 114)
- Benjamin M. Selekman and Stephen H. Fuller: Problems in Labor Relations, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 115)
- Daniel L. Shapiro and Vanessa Liu: Psychology of a Stable Peace, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Tim Weiner: Remembering Brainwashing, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Secret U.S. Endorsement of Severe Interrogations of Terror Suspects, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Herbert C. Kelman: The Social Context of Torture: Policy Process and Authority Structure (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Debra Meyerson: Swift Trust and Temporary Groups, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Nicholas Dujmovic: Two CIA Prisoners in China, 1952-73, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Haviland Smith: The U.S. Response to Terrorism: A Fundamentally Flawed Strategy, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Tim Grant: Unifying Planning and Control Using an OODA-based Architecture, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- The Unstudied Art of Interrogation. Scott Shane, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Jared R. Curhan, Et. Al: What Do People Value When They Negotiate?, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Dilemmas (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Does the Concept of Trust Have Any Relevance to Interrogation? (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Robert Fine (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Forcing and Fostering Organizational Change (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Negotiating the Negotiation (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Notes from Interrogation (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Pedagogs (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Proposed Research Plan (Box 7, Folder 18)
- MITRE Paper Work, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Handwritten Notes (Box 7, Folder 20)
- NPOA Thurston - - AAA 11 390 01171 12, CD/DVD (Box 9, Folder 1)
  pulled from box 2/ff17
- Tamiment Library, CD/DVD (Box 10, Folder 1)
  pulled from box 4/ff7
- Thurston - 5/12/12 -- Radio, 2012; CD/DVD (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Bill LaCara Photos - 2/15/12 -- Civil Rights Book, 2012; CD/DVD (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Power of Partnership (L+M)P, CD/DVD (Box 13, Folder 1)
  pulled from box 6/ff90 & 91
- Robert McKersie -- 2012012 4084637, CD/DVD (Box 14, Folder 1)
  This disc contains: CULR - 0092-0966-01; CULR - 0120-1392-02; CULR - 0120-1392-04
- Manuscript - R.B. McKersie -- Civil Rights in Chicago, 1960s -- 2/16/12 (DUP), 2012; CD/DVD (Box 15, Folder 1)
- McKersie_HydeParkMap.eps - revised 02.03.2012, CD/DVD (Box 16, Folder 1)